<LAURA DIAZ FRONTEND DEVELOPER />

lauradiaz1586@gmail.com My portfolio

I'm a Frontend Developer with two years of experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development and proactive feature optimization.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Dorothy | Jun 2021 - Present
Frontend development of different company
products. I identify and fix bugs/technical issues
before and after deploying. Depending on the
project needs, I implemented Redux and Context
API for state management.

Tech stack: NextJs (ReactJs Framework), Redux.

Frontend Developer

Freelance | Jun 2020 - May 2021 A freelance project for a Graphic and Typeface designer is a responsive website built in NextJs. I worked closely with the designer. https://ferminguerrero.com/ .

Tech stack: NextJs (ReactJs Framework).

Cabin Crew

Emirates Airline | May 2016 - Jul 2020 Safety and security. Customer service.

Workforce Management Analyst

Telefónica | Dec 2014 - Apr 2016 Analyzed, controlled, and managed the services in the Customer Service Department. Executed actions and launched the contingency plan for any situation that may impact Customer Service performance.

Workforce Management Analyst

Directv | Apr 2013 - Dec 2014

My work consisted of controlling in real-time the behavior of the Customer Service Center's traffic calls. Ensured compliance with a high service level. Created reports about customer service agent's performance. I Solved problems that affected the business.

Customer Care

Directv | Apr 2010 - Apr 2013

Receptionist / Administrative

Big Ben Institute | Jun 2009 - Mar 2010

SKILLS

- HTML5.
- CSS3.
- Javascript.
- ReactJs.
- Redux.
- NextJs.
- Git.
- Browser dev tools.

EDUCATION

Frontend Development Bootcamp

CourseIt | Mar 2020 - Aug 2020 Frontend development coding bootcamp with an extension of +200 hours

Skills: HTML5, CSS, Javascript (ES6), ReactJs.